[English subtitles are available]
[Song of the Moon]
[Episode 29]
My Lord, please go to Immortal Palace
to open the Four Seasons Monument.
Release the God of the Moonlight,
and undo the curse of our people.
Release the God of the Moonlight!
Undo the curse of our people!
Do you know
that the person under the Four Seasons Monument
has long been corrupted by evil spirit,
and is no longer the pure God of the Moonlight?
Once he comes out,
he will definitely bring chaos to the Three Realms
and kill many innocent lives.
When I was at Immortal Palace,
Supreme God once entered my dream,
and promised to undo the curse of my people
as long as I could release him.
The rest
has nothing to do with us.
My Lord, please go to Immortal Palace
to open the Four Seasons Monument,
Release the God of the Moonlight,
and undo the curse of our people.
Release the God of the Moonlight!
Undo the curse of our people!
Brother.
I'll make my own decision on this matter.
Anyone refuses to accept it
should do his best
to stabilize
the demon world first.
Or
how about extracting your divine spirit
to take out the power of the Demon King in it?
Get out!
Brother.
Brother! Brother!
Fortunately.
Although the monument is broken,
there is
no evil spirit escaping from it.
It's hard to say.
What if the evil spirit has escaped from Immortal Palace?
The escaped evil spirit has limited power.
Besides I haven't heard anything about it yet.
News from Marquis Wuyang's Mansion.
The human world is in chaos.
I heard that Demon Palace
is also in chaos.
There may also be someone from the Demons who will take the opportunity to make troubles.
Does the information you mentioned
mean that
the power of that thing under the monument has become stronger?
The evil spirit
originated from the desire in the human heart.
Under the nourishment of the evil spirit,
tiny human desires
can be lured and expanded
and gradually spread in the Three Realms.
That's why
we must protect the Four Seasons Monument,
so that the evil thing has no chance of escaping.
Both worlds of humans and demons have been affected by evil spirit,
why can't there be any evil spirit here?
Could it be
that it turned into a human form
and escaped our pursuit?
Nonsense.
The evil spirit
can only affect the mind of a person.
It cannot turn into human form.
A small amount may not be enough to do so.
But if it is strong enough
to confuse some people's minds
or possess someone whose mind is unstable,
then it is not necessarily so.
You mean...
Pay more attention to the situation in the Three Realms
to avoid further accidents.
Brother.
It's my fault.
I was the one who took away the power of the Demon King,
and joined forces with them to persecute you.
I'm sorry, brother.
You first took away the power of the Demon King,
put we Aquatic Demons in a desperate situation,
and then led them to forcefully persecute me.
Now you are on your knees begging for my forgiveness.
Fu.
In fact, you are expecting
I will definitely forgive you
no matter how sad I am
if you do so,
right?
Yes.
I am too cunning
and too scheming.
But the power of the Demon King has been refined by me.
Now,
I will return the power of the Demon King
together with my divine spirit
to you.
Fu!
Don't worry, Fu.
I'll figure it out.
Could you please
undo the curse for my people?
Fu colluded with Bai Feng to cause chaos in Immortal Palace.
Why should I help you?
It seems that you don't care
about Fu's injury.
You probably don't know
that his divine spirit was damaged
because you broke his water energy pill.
In order to save himself,
he took away the power of the Demon King that stabilized the demon world.
It was because of me.
It was not your fault.
It was because Fu was too immature.
I won't force you
if you don't want to help us.
Demon King,
you're late.
Immortal has just left
for Marquis Wuyang's Mansion.
Could it be that Liu Shao is there?
You are too weak to fight me.
Don't be afraid of her.
We have the Protection Spell here.
Is that all you have got?
When I was a senior here,
you didn't even exist yet.
Bai Feng.
How dare you!
You are really here.
Liu Shao.
I didn't expect that you could also become a disciple here.
I was the one who didn't expect
you to still be so rampant.
Haven't you been punished enough by Immortal Palace?
Don't count on anyone from Immortal Palace to save you.
They are all hypocrites.
You all will die today!
I beat you once.
I can still beat you
today.
You're still talking nonsense, aren’t you?
Senior,
with the Protection Spell here, we don’t need to be afraid of this evil woman.
Really?
Damn.
Senior Liu Shao was taken out of the Protection Spell by that whirlwind.
[Marquis Wuyang's Mansion]
Bai Feng!
What else can you do besides playing tricks?
Everyone hates you.
And you live like a demon!
You used poison?
No.
It's not demon poison.
You're right.
But it's a poison that even Immortal is in awe of.
Why would you still protect her?
Why?
Brother.
Demon King.
It was here that Liu Shao was plotted against by Bai Feng
and disappeared.
It was Illusion Spell.
The moment I broke through the illusion,
Bai Feng took Liu Shao away.
Luo Ge.
Use the Moon Bell to find her.
Bai Feng knew Moon Bell very well,
so she cut off my connection with that bell.
Luo Ge,
you are exhausted.
Take a rest first.
I'll go find her.
Let's split up.
Luo Ge.
Brother!
I'll go too.
You guys can look around as well.
Okay.
[Marquis Wuyang's Mansion]
Fu's divine spirit was damaged
because you broke his water energy pill.
Why would I still worry about that bad guy?
Let me help you.
Without the power of the Demon King,
they would be thrown out of the water.
People from Aquatic Demons
do die out of water.
Luo Ning.
Luo Ning!
Did you intend
to kill her just now?
General Fu,
only the demon power of Demon King in White
can barely maintain the stability
of Demon Palace now.
People from Aquatic Demons are thrown out of the water frequently.
And there are often demons with malicious intentions outside
waiting to take demon energy from our people.
I had to set a lot of traps around.
But I didn't expect them to hurt Fairy Luo Ning.
This...
I made it very clear
the day my divine spirit was wounded
that I had done so many things
just to keep her by my side.
From now on,
none of you are allowed to hurt her.
Yes.
Luo Ning.
Have a good sleep.
When I finish my work,
you will understand
that you can only stay by my side.
Well done.
I didn't save your life
and try so hard to heal you in vain.
I want to kill her.
Keeping her
is more useful than killing her.
What is this?
A thousand years ago,
Xie Lingqi secretly
brought this Poisonous Incense out
from Yin-yang Cave without telling Immortal Palace.
Poisonous Incense?
Those who smelled this incense
would not be able to activate their spiritual veins,
and would lose their minds
to become demons after a period of time.
I'd like to see
if Luo Ge
is willing to kill her
by then.
Send her back to Luo Ge?
I won't do that.
Liu Shao, I will torture you to death.
Bai Feng?
Liu Shao.
Liu Shao!
Come on.
He Na?
Why am I here?
You were kidnapped by Bai Feng
and poisoned by Moon Poison.
Luo Ge and I have been looking for you.
I've found you now,
and I have notified Immortal Palace.
Just take some rest first.
Will I be fine?
Moon Poison is extremely poisonous
and comes from Yin-yang Cave in Immortal Palace.
But the cave has been closed for thousands of years.
I don't know who brought this poison out,
and why it was obtained by Bai Feng.
I can't use my spiritual power
right now.
Is it because of this Moon Poison?
Don't worry.
Sun Spring in Yin-yang Cave
can cure this poison.
Besides,
Moon Poison has no effect
on the people from Aquatic Demons.
No.
I can't implicate you anymore.
It is me who should go,
not you.
Or
how about
I take you there?
Liu Shao.
Where are you?
Luo Ge!
Luo Ge.
Liu Shao has been rescued by He Na.
But
she was poisoned by Moon Poison.
Moon Poison?
That's something from Yin-yang Cave.
I could only think of Xie Lingqi
who would own it
in the entire Immortal Palace.
Yes.
Moon Poison was given to him by me.
He promised me to reopen Yin-yang Cave.
But I don't know
who he gave it to.
You don't have to ask him.
Why don't we just go to Yin-yang Cave to find it?
Speaking of it,
Lord Shang wanted to open Xilun Formation back then,
[Yin-yang Cave]
but was afraid that he would be turned into stone by the backlash of the formation.
So he was as anxious as you are
to find Sun Spring to protect himself.
But have you ever wondered
why Lord Shang
would have let us take the risk
if Sun Spring was so easy to get?
Liu Shao, we must get out as soon as possible.
Is there something wrong?
I'm not sure.
It's just that this boundary
seems to have a seriou problem.
A seriou problem?
But it was pretty easy
when I just came in.
The boundary at the entrance was set up by Immortal Palace a thousand years ago.
But I felt Sun's aura
on that boundary.
So this boundary was once set by God of the Sun?
The boundary set by the Immortal Palace was easy to open,
but I'm worried that when we try to get out later...
I'm afraid it's easy to get in this Yin-yang Cave,
but it won't be so easy to get out.
It is said that ten thousand years ago,
God of the Sun cleaned up the evil spirit in Yin-yang Cave,
and the remaining impurities turned into Sun Spring and Moon Poison.
And he set a boundary here.
Anyway, we have to find Sun Spring
to detoxify you first.
Back then Lord Shang refused to go in
because he was afraid that he wouldn't be able to get out.
My dad was not such a timid person.
He was busy stabilizing the Four Seasons Monument,
and couldn't come in person,
so he asked you to get Sun Spring.
You are so naive.
You didn't know
where the cave's exit was,
so your father barely opened a crack
on Sun Boundary.
But there was
more than just Sun Boundary in this cave,
but also the Moon Poison formed by the hatred of the two gods.
As long as someone touched Sun Spring,
Moon Poison would come out with it.
And inhaling this poison would cause you to lose your mind
and become a demon who only knows killing.
In order to get Sun Spring,
your father, Lord Shang,
did not hesitate to let the disciples of the three palaces enter here in batches.
I was prepared back then.
So I brought Moon Poison and Sun Spring
to get out before the crack closed.
Moon Poison is too dangerous. I'll keep it.
You've been poisoned. Take Sun Spring with you.
If I can't get out,
[Xie Lingqi's Junior Sister, Wu Shiwei]
you can detoxify yourself.
Shiwei!
Shiwei. Shiwei.
Shiwei! Shiwei!
Let me carry you.
You go first.
Leave me alone. You go first.
It's too late.
I won't leave you here.
Let's go together.
Just leave!
Shiwei!
Shiwei?
Why?
Senior.
Shiwei...
You...
I can't go
without Sun Spring.
No.
I'll stay here to look for Sun Spring
and wait for you to come and save me.
No.
Shiwei.
I escaped.
But the others
were trapped there
forever.
Among those people
were my fellow disciples,
my best friend,
and
my junior sister.
Yin-yang Cave was filled with the helpless despair
and the pain of being unable to escape.
So there spawned countless evil spirits.
The Four Seasons Monument has also become unstable because of this.
So Lord Shang had to seal it.
No one...
No one was there to save my junior sister.
No one was there to save Shiwei.
You want to save Wu Shiwei?
Yes!
I'm going to open Yin-yang Cave
to save her.
It has been a thousand years.
She has been waiting for me for a thousand years.
Luo Ge!
Take me with you!
Aren't you going to punish me?
Take me to Yin-yang Cave with you.
Even if I have to die,
I want to be with Shiwei.
You didn't melt in Bone Melting Pool,
so you're a kind person and don't deserve to die.
You don't have to go to Yin-yang Cave.
I am the only one who knows where the crack is
in the entire Immortal Palace.
I was the only survivor back then.
No one can take you out
except me.
Time is running out.
Just take me there
if you don't want Liu Shao to become a demon.
How do you feel?
Are you okay?
With your water energy and elixir,
I'm much better now.
This is...
Be careful.
It is Moon Poison.
It comes out with Sun Spring.
He Na, be careful!
He Na!
He Na.
Come on.
Be careful.
What?
My brother went to Yin-yang Cave?
He could only go there
if he wanted to save Miss Liu.
But how could Liu Shao be rescued by my brother?
Shouldn't she...
You're awake.
Where are you going?
Lie down and take some rest.
Leave me alone.
If I didn't take care of you,
would you still be here and be angry with me?
Didn't you say that you don't want to see me for the rest of your life?
Didn't you crush my water energy pill?
Why did you come here again?
I just wanted to see
how serious your injuries are,
which caused you to take the power of the Demon King
at the risk of destroying your entire race.
So
you came to see me
because you were worried about me,
right?
I am not worried about you.
You almost killed Liu Shao and my brother
with the power of the water spirit bead.
So even if you got hurt,
you deserved it.
Yes.
I shouldn't have...
I shouldn't have hurt your family
and your fellow disciples.
Even if I would die from serious injuries,
I deserved it.
I... I saw
one of your people
die in front of me just like that.
Over the years,
I have seen too many of our people
choose to end their lives
because they could not bear the torture
of staying here.
That's why I did the wrong thing
that made you sad.
I won't do this again.
Shiwei.
Shiwei!
He Na!
Liu Shao?
Go, He Na.
Leave me here.
These disciples
have lost their minds.
We can't beat them.
I won't leave you alone.
He Na, your hand...
I always thought
that if I become stronger, I won't drag anyone down.
But I still dragged you down.
Liu Shao.
I never thought you were a burden.
If I could die here with you,
maybe it would be another kind of fate for us.
Remember the Water Hyacinth jade pendant I gave you?
Actually,
that was what I prepared for my Demon Queen.
He Na...
He Na!
Luo Ge?
He had spent a lot of thought on the Four Seasons Monument,
and now he went to Yin-yang Cave.
He got into so much trouble
because of Liu Shao.
If this continues,
when will Ge become Supreme God?
He only cares about Liu Shao
and He Na,
not the Three Realms at all.
Immortal Master,
it's not appropriate for you to say so.
If he hadn't helped stabilize the demon world,
the chaos in the demon world
would have affected the Three Realms.
Then what about Yin-yang Cave?
Is that where he should go?
What do you want him to do?
Do you want him to watch
his beloved die?
I did it for his own good.
You
can't do anything else
but help him.
Senior.
Master Shang.
Why did they
go to Yin-yang Cave?
What?
Both my brother and your brother entered Yin-yang Cave?
Yes.
It is said that strange things
will happen in Yin-yang Cave.
After my brother entered,
I tried to contact him
with our Demon Palace's unique spell.
But
he never replied to me.
In that case,
could they already be in danger?
If he hadn't been in danger,
he would have replied to me
knowing that I was worried about him.
Are you going back?
You can
at least know their situation
as soon as possible if you stay here.
I'm going to wait until dawn.
If he hasn't replied to me by then,
I'll go in and save them.
If my brother and your brother teamed up
and still encountered big trouble inside,
it would be useless for you to go in.
He is my elder brother,
the Demon King of my race.
Even if I die inside,
he has to come out alive.
You should understand, right?
Then I'll wait here with you.
If there is no messages from them tomorrow,
I will enter Yin-yang Cave with you.
He Na.
Luo Ge.
I thought I could bring Liu Shao here
to detoxify her.
But my Water Shield
didn't work here.
The forbidden spell was set by God of the Sun
ten thousand years ago.
Not to mention your Water Shield,
even Luo Ge's
Lotus Spell
can't be cast here.
You shouldn't be here.
I gave you Moon Bell
just to know if you are safe.
You can give it back to me now
if you don't want me to care about you.
You already gave it to me.
How can you take it back?
I thought you didn't want it.
Of course I want it.
Stop it.
I'm going to heal you.
Shiwei.
I will definitely bring you home
wherever you are.
Fu.
Liu Shao has already met me,
so did Luo Ge,
so don't worry.
What's wrong?
Any news?
Liu Shao,
your brother
and my brother have already met up.
They should be safe for now.
They haven't come out yet?
It seems that this matter is a bit strange.
But
if the problem could not be solved
when your brother and my brother have joined forces,
it shoule not be solved
by anyone else in this world.
That's true.
Would you like to go to bed and rest for a while?
No need.
I'll just wait them here.
Let me know if you have any news.
Or do you need me to make perfume with you?
Don't bother.
Go ahead with your business.
I'll do it myself.
Fu...
Luo Ning,
please don't leave me,
okay?
The Life Gate of the Four Seasons Monument is connected to Bone Melting Pool,
and its Death Gate is connected to Yin-yang Cave.
Thousands of years of resentment have accumulated here.
If we enter it suddenly,
it will definitely trigger the evil spirit fluctuations of the demonized disciples,
causing
Four Seasons Monument to become unstable.
Therefore,
we have to cast spells and get Sun Spring as soon as possible.
And we need a guard.
Otherwise...
I knew it.
You stay here.
I'm going to distract them.
He Na.
Go get Sun Spring.
Xie Lingqi,
protect Liu Shao.
Follow me
if you want Sun Spring.
Luo Ge!
Liu Shao!
Luo Ge's spiritual power is superb,
he should be fine.
Be careful!
You are...
Xie Lingqi!
Shiwei!
It has been a thousand years.
I'm here to save you now.
I'll take you back.
I won't leave you here.
Let's go together.
Hurry up!
I'll stay here looking for Sun Spring,
and wait for you to come and save me.
Shiwei!
No.
My surname is Xie.
-I'm your senior. -Shiwei. Shiwei will come back.
What a nice name.
We once agreed
that I would get you out.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I'm
waiting for someone.
Wu Shiwei
is waiting for Xie Lingqi.
Shiwei.
Sorry.
I'm late.
It has been a thousand years.
You have suffered too much.
Shiwei.
Let's go home.
I'll take you home, okay?
Shiwei.
Shiwei, look at me.
I'm Xie Lingqi,
the one who promised to protect you forever.
Do you remember?
You said you would wait for me to save you.
Senior Xie.
It's me.
I'm here to save you.
You finally came.
Luo Ge!
You are hurt?
I'm fine.
How is it?
Have you got Sun Spring?
Yes. Let's retreat.
Okay.
I know there is a safe place.
Follow me.
Let's go.
Senior.
Do I look ugly?
No.
You look so pretty.
Come on.
I'll take you to Luo Ge.
He is the current Immortal.
Come on.
Immortal should be able to deal with those
demonized disciples.
Why was he seriously injured?
It should be caused by Yin-yang Power in this cave.
Don't worry.
I observed the terrain here just now,
and set up formations around.
That cost me a little immortal energy.
Liu Shao.
Her immortal energy
was severely eroded by Moon Poison,
so she had to take Sun Spring immediately.
Otherwise she would completely lose her mind
just like those disciples.
Our spiritual powers are working against each other.
If this continues,
we will never get out.
No.
The disciples in the cave will come soon
once they smell Sun Spring.
You have no time to refine it.
We must get out first.
Sealing this Moon Bell inside her body
can temporarily protect her immortal energy.
Xie Lingqi, lead the way.
We've been here for too long.
Now we need to find that crack as soon as possible.
If we delay a little longer
we will not be able to get out.
I am affected by Yin-yang Power
and cannot use water energy at all.
Luo Ge,
we're counting on you.
Immortal
should be able to barely open this boundary
and buy us some time.
They're coming.
I'll go stop them first.
Shiwei!
Luo Ge, what should we do?